<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Solopie's Website</title><link>https://www.solopie.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Solopie's Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.solopie.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>https://www.solopie.com/p/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.solopie.com/p/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.solopie.com/p/hello-world/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Hello World!" />&lt;h1 id="hello-">Hello 👋
&lt;/h1>&lt;p>My name is Jesse, I usually use the tag &lt;code>Solopie&lt;/code> and like all things programming, especially the security aspects.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m currently a Penetration Tester at &lt;a class="link" href="https://tantosec.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Tanto Security&lt;/a> and aim to be just as good as the real hackers out there!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve done CTFs here and there for about 4-5 years and aim to be an all-rounder. I do attempt to tackle the web category last though since I&amp;rsquo;m always doing web stuff at work anyway and to force myself to learn something new (web can get pretty cool too though). I&amp;rsquo;ve always been interested in tinkering as well so I&amp;rsquo;ve done my fair share of programming and want to eventually translate to creating devices that can manipulate the real world (IOT devices, robots, vehicle automation).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Created this page to try out the hype around &lt;a class="link" href="https://gohugo.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Hugo&lt;/a> which I&amp;rsquo;m pretty late too &lt;em>(I&amp;rsquo;ve procrastinated doing this for 2 years)&lt;/em> and have recently been trying to get back into CTFs so might as well have somewhere to post writeups to! Considering doing educational content too but will be super basic stuff, we will see 👀&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Looking forward to producing some hopefully interesting content. Feel free to connect with me on &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/solopie/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Linkedin&lt;/a> if you wanna reach out!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>